I would say the climate change is like my calling
What i really  like is that it is a natural solution
We're taking the carbon  that's in the atmosphere,
bring it back into the ground and into biomass
and therefore reducing the level
of carbon dioxide  in the atmosphere
and through that addressing  climate change
and hopefully  reduce the impact it will have.
At Terraformation, we are also addressing other issues like
the lose of biodiversity by actual creating
native habitats with the trees or plants we plant.
So we can address multiple issues with that approach
and that's really, really great
We need that to happen, it's time.