The world can seem
like  a kind  of  a  harrowing place right now
but to actually be  a part of the solution
to global climate change is just very gratifying
i'm at home in the forest
and just want to make sure that my children
and future generations have that same exprience
So, that's why we're here collecting the seed
and planting the plants and do the work
so they can have that same experience.
Terraformation have came up with a plan
and they're involving other people as well.
And so it's going to be the growing phenomeno
that with a lot of help, it just  can be  attainable
It just  give me hope that  we're doing the right thing
and that climate change can be solved.