The effects of the climate change seen to be accelerating
at an exponential rate
Plants aiming at solving some portion of the problem
in 50 years , or like over next 100 years,
are possible fatally too slow
In order to fully decarbonize the grid
and then remove all of the excess CO2 that's been released,
we probably have to achieve that, in about 30 years
And event that's kind of a dangerously long timeframe
In order to have like 10 or 20 years of forest maturity,
it means we have to do all the out planting in 10 years
If the goal is to plant 1 trillion trees
we need 2 trillion seeds
So fist we go out into the field.
Once we have  the seed , we bring them back here to
either the nursery or the seed bank will process the seed
clean them up , get them ready to dry
This is gonna allow people store the seeds
for future restoration sites
So we bank some seeds and we plant some seeds
So we bring them here into the nursery
The greenhouse are exactly what you see here
It's the same greenhouse that are gonna be shipped
all over the world
So it just gives people the tools to grow the plants
We know it can be done here
We're doing it successfully and they can do it too.
We pick up the plant in the nursery
that preselected for that planting day.
Each tree gets a little irrigation line
and gets watered every second for a little bit
to help it in the beginning
give them nice little bit of soil, fertilizer
We're using diatomaceous earth to keep bugs
from climbing on them
After the  planting, we go through
and take the geo location of each point
And then the information get stored in the geo databases
for the geographic information system.
Eventually once they're all established
they'll support each other.
They'll cool this area
which will help the rain and moisture stay here
And so we can turn this desert into a forest again.
There's a lot involved that needs to happen
to able to get these trees into the ground.
And it's a lot of work, but  it's all worth it.
It just, it feels good to be doing the work
to be putting these practices in place
and to be moving forward